leisurearts.com 2005-12-15

# Leisure Arts

|   
---  
**Crafts& Needlework**  
**Cooking& Entertaining**  
**Home& Garden**  
**Scrapbooking**  
**Christmas**  
  
**Quick Tips**  
  
**New Releases**  
**Store Locator**  
**Commitment to Quality**  
**Let Us Hear From You**  
**Corrections**  
**Our Links**  
**For Wholesale  
inquiries visit  
  
5701 Ranch Drive  
Little Rock, AR 72223-9633  
1-800-526-5111

Copyright © 2005  
Leisure Arts, Inc.  
All Rights Reserved.  
Privacy Policy  
  
| 

Thank you for visiting LeisureArts.com, a Time Inc. site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Time Inc. site. Click here for a list of the Time Inc. businesses whose sites are governed by this Privacy Notice.

The Information We Collect

At some Time Inc. sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At some other Time Inc. sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of Time Inc. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Time Inc.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

If a Time Inc. site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Time Inc. who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. For instructions on how to opt out from such disclosures, please send an e-mail, along with your first and last name, to [customer_service@leisurearts.com](mailto:customer_service@leisurearts.com).

Time Inc. may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please send an e-mail, along with your first and last name, to [customer_service@leisurearts.com](mailto:customer_service@leisurearts.com).

Finally, Time Inc. sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Advertisers and Sponsors

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Time Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Time Inc. has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. The Time Inc. site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

Time Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). For more information on this site's use of such third-parties, please click here.

Cookies

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

How You can Access or Correct Information

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this Time Inc. site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please send an e-mail, along with your first and last name, to [customer_service@leisurearts.com](mailto:customer_service@leisurearts.com).

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Special Note for Parents

The site you are visiting is one of the Time Inc. general audience sites. For more information about our online privacy practices for children's sites, consult the privacy notice at the children's site in which you are interested.

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Time Inc. online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at customer_service@leisurearts.com.

Time Warner businesses whose sites are governed by our Privacy Policy:  
BUSINESS 2.0  
ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY  
FORTUNE  
INSTYLE  
MUTUAL FUNDS  
PARENTING  
PEOPLE  
PEOPLE EN ESPANOL  
REAL SIMPLE  
TEEN PEOPLE  
TIME  
COASTAL LIVING  
COOKING LIGHT  
HEALTH  
LEISURE ARTS  
OXMOOR HOUSE  
PROGRESSIVE FARMER  
SOUTHERN ACCENTS  
SOUTHERN LIVING  
SUNSET  
SUNSET BOOKS  
FIELD & STREAM  
FREEZE  
MOTOCROSS  
OUTDOOR LIFE  
POPULAR SCIENCE  
RIDE BMX  
SALT WATER SPORTSMAN  
SKATEBOARDING  
SKI  
SKIING  
SNOWBOARDING  
STANCE  
SURF  
THIS OLD HOUSE  
YACHTING  
TIME INC. HOME ENTERTAINMENT  
TIME LIFE INC.

We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and to conduct research about the advertisements. For more about these third parties and their privacy/opt out policies, click on the links below:

| Atlas DMT: | [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or  
<http://www.atlasdmt.com/privacy/>  
---|---  
DoubleClick: | [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or  
<http://www.doubleclick.com/us/>  
MediaPlex: | [http://www.mediaplex.com](http://www.mediaplex.com/)  
PGI: | <http://citi.bridgetrack.com/privacy.htm>  
Dynamic Logic: | <http://www.dynamiclogic.com/index.php>  
Millward Brown IntelliQuest | [http://www.intelliquest.com](http://www.intelliquest.com/)
